[{"answer": "No, I'm picking you up", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "OK, now before I go, does anybody else need to be picked up?  I'm still gonna go", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, OK", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "OK, look, this isn't the first time somebody's said something to me about this, but, I don't know... I always made excuses about it, like... uhhh... 'I'm just a social drinker,' or, 'C'mon, it's Flag Day.", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, well, we have to celebrate. You know what we should do? We should do, like, a soap opera theme", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hey Rach, what time do you get off? We're all gonna do something tonight", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Ummmm.... well, actually I'm already done, but I...I kinda got plans", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah... I, uhh... I have a... I have a date", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh.... my... God", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Not that bad? Did you hear the hammer story", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes, yes I am. Are you a, uh, a friend of my friend's", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Are you a, uh, friend of my friend's", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Actually, I'm a... kind of a.... you know, a... dat", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Actually, I'm a... kind of a.... you know, a... dat", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah, I'm her date", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "A date", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, oh, you're... uh... you're, oh you're the date", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, we're not seeing each other, so...", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, Phoebs. I'm dating my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey, you listen", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, let me finish", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, no, let me finish", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, you let me fini..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh God, you fell off the wagon", "docId": "210russ.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What about me", "qsentId": 28}]